[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHEERING]
Gandang Gabi,Kapamilya and Kapuso!
[AUDIENCE] Gandang Gabi, Vice!
[VICE] Yes!
Do I look beautiful tonight?
[AUDIENCE SHOUTING] Yes!
But the real question isare you beautiful?
[AUDIENCE] Yes!
Yes, as long as we're together,we're all beautiful!
What are you waitingfor this time?
You should go to bed already.
You all want to laugh again?
You want to hearcrude stuff again?
[AUDIENCE SHOUTING] Yes!
You want to see usget naughty here again.
- [AUDIENCE] Yes!- I know what you want.
You want to have funand laugh together here.
But when I get bashed,you all sleep early.
- You don't even defend me.- [LAUGHTER SFX]
Well, it's Sunday again.
Are you ready for another roundof good vibes and fun?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
It's fun, isn't it?
That feeling of being happy andpositive before we go to sleep.
We'll eradicate loneliness,sadness, and unhappiness first.
Eradicate? That's a big word!
[COMICAL SFX]
When was the last timeyou used that term?
Eradicate.
When do you use it?Do you still use that word?
We'll eradicate loneliness
and put an end to sadness.
Just like that!
How poetic, right?
That's the kind of words that
our great singers andcomposers use, right?
Our best OPM singers andcomposers use those words.
Are you guys in love?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING] Yes!
Are you feelingthe love tonight?
Yes!
[VICE] Yes!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Well, for those whoaren't really in love--
[AUDIENCE CHEERING, SCREAMING]
What?
- Why? Do you feel--- Are you in love?
Am I in love? Yes.
I am so in love...
And I am so in lovewith being in love.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[TETAY LAUGHING]
[VICE] It sounds likeyou're mimicking me.
How annoying. Why don'tyou fall down there yet?
But it talking about lovefeels great, doesn't it?
Being loved issuch a great feeling.
And you don't have to bewith someone to feel love.
Right?
It's such a blessing ifsomeone gives you love.
But if you don't have anyoneto give love to you,
you can give love to yourself.
[AUDIENCE] Yes!
[VICE] Especially onChristmas Day.
Give love on Christmas Day.
Because during Christmas,doesn't it...
During Christmas,love just feels natural.
- Right?- [AUDIENCE] Yes!
Why does Vince seem sad?
[AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING]
He doesn't talk much whenthe topic is about love.
Give a hand to our Geng Gang.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Why do you look upset whenwe're talking about love?
Here's the thing, Meme.
What are your thoughtsabout love?
- My thoughts on love?- Yeah.
It will just come.
[AUDIENCE SQUEALS]
And I'm just right herewaiting for her to come.
How chic, you're waiting.
You're just like a princelying under a tree
waiting for the Adarna birdto poop on you
until you get turned into stone.
[CHUCKLING]
You looked like you werewhispering to each other.
What were you talkingabout love?
I was asking them for advice.
And I was surprised thatthey have love lives.
[LAUGHING]
[VINCE] Look at whatshe's holding! Are you a witch?
She brought a doll.
[VICE] Throw that away.I'm scared of things like that.
You look like Bakekang.Do you know Bakekang?
- [TETAY CHUCKLES]- I don't.
Bakekang is a characterportrayed by Nora Aunor.
She lost her daughter Kristal
so she claimed a dollas her daughter.
- [VERNA] Ah.- Why do you have a doll?
Well, since you're lookingfor love...
[AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
You had no idea thatyou already had a kid.
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Meet your daughter.
[AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
Verna? Inverna?
- [VICE LAUGHS] Inverna.- [CHUCKLING]
That's really the nameexactly what you call it.
Verna is in a relationship.
Tetay also has a love life.
Yes.
The guy with the looks isthe one who has none.
He's handsomebut he's a loser!
Kidding!
Your looks alone won'tmake you loved, boy!
- Yes! It doesn't depend on it.- Loser!
Hey! My mom loves me.
- Huh?- Mama loves me.
But your mother lovesher husband more than you.
- Yes!- Kidding.
What were you asking Tetayand Verna about love?
I was asking how to have
a lasting andsuccessful relationship.
As well as how to court someone.
- Where can I find someone?- Ah...
You should ask Vernaabout courtships because
she's been led astraya few times already.
- Just like a cat?- She just keeps coming back.
She's been led astray many timesnow but she keeps coming back.
[VERNA] It's Vince's fault.
If you just courted me before,
then you wouldn'tbe lonely right now.
- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING]- [SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYS]
What would you advice Vinceabout love and finding love?
I told him to just not rush it.
It's just like howit happened with you, right?
You said before that you didn'texpect to find love anymore.
You said you didn't believein love for so long.
But Ion suddenly cameinto your life, right?
[SQUEALING]
[VICE SHUSHES]
[TETAY] The more you push it,the more you look for it,
that's when love becomesmore elusive.
Right, it's like fate isplaying with you.
When want someone so badly,you won't have them.
It's just like whenfate plays with her.
Ghoul! Ghoul! [CHUCKLES]
- [COMICAL SFX]- Hey!
I never had a problem with love.
- Of course.- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
I'm the one who givespeople love problems.
- Yes.- Of course.
Any family will have a problemif you become part of theirs.
[VICE] But you know...
Like what he said,love will come to you.
And as long as ithasn't come yet...
Make yourself happy.
Remember, you won't be lonely...
as long as you have a hand.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Look, my hands are gettingwounds already. [CHUCKLES]
It's true! He hurthis hand yesterday.
He asked me for a tissue paper.
No, that's from the gym.
But as long as you have a hand,
your hands can do thingsthat will make you happy.
What can we do with our handsthat will bring us happiness?
Um, tree planting.
- Ahh.- Right.
- Cooking.- Cooking, tidying up.
- Yes.- Cleaning stuff up.
Yes and, um...
Lending your hand tothe less fortunate ones.
When was the last timeyou were happy?
- [AUDIENCE CHUCKLES]- I think last year.
- What?!- Last year?!
[TETAY] Your guy doesn't knowhow to court someone.
He doesn't knowhow to court a girl.
Well, you shouldn't ask themfor advice.
Their cases are unique.
- Yeah.- Let's ask the people here.
Who here is in love?
- Who here is in love?- Be honest, okay?
Who's in love?
Who?
[VICE] Wow. They reallyraised their hands up.
They really said,"We are in love."
They raised their handslike that.
Are you a couple?
[VICE] Are you two together or
do you each have a partner whodoesn't know you're together?
Oh, you're really a couple.
What's your name?
Hi, I'm Ram.
He's Ram, and you?You're Bhutan.
Ram and Bhutan.
- Rambutan.- [LAUGHING]
[VERNA] That's a fruit!
[CHUCKLING]
I'm Ram. I'm Korean from Bhutan.
Rambutan.
- [LAUGHTER SFX]- Ram, and?
Anne Ray.
So, how long have youbeen together?
Um, married since May 2026.
- Ah, that's so recent!- Yes.
May, August...
Ah, two! It's only beentwo months.
May, June, July, August.
Oh, right. June goes after May.
[LAUGHING]
Dumb ass.
[TETAY] You're beautiful but...
You may think I'm perfectbut I'm really stupid.
[CHUCKLES]
So, four months!
And you're already married.
[EXCLAIMS] Oh my god, Vince.You're getting more upset.
Lucky you!
[VICE] When you seepeople like them,
a happy couple who arein love and married,
how do you feel?
Do you feel sad for yourself?
Not really because I also alwayssee how happy my parents are.
And their love just inspires me.
Seeing them happy togetherand all that.
[VICE] What you've just saidis really beautiful.
It's nice when your inspirationis coming from your own home.
- Yeah.- Right?
The beautiful conceptof love is being...
exhibited inside your own home.
Where did you two meet?
We were classmatesin 4th grade.
You were classmates in 4th gradeand got married in 5th grade?
- [CHUCKLING]- Ah, no.
You've known each othersince elementary,
but when did youbecome a couple?
In high school or college?
Just five years ago,during the pandemic.
How old are you now?
- Five years.- I meant your age.
I'm 35. He's 34.
Ah, so you weren't a couplewhen you were still in school?
Didn't you like each otherin the beginning?
- Only she did.- Hey!
- [LAUGHING]- [TETAY] She said, "Hey!"
You didn't like herbut she liked you?
How handsome.I'll photocopy your face later.
I'll put your face onthe machine myself.
[LAUGHING]
Twelve copies back to back.
You handsome bastard.
Really?
Did you start off as friends or?
- Yes, we were friends first.- We were really friends.
Has your friendship helped you?
It's a huge help, yeah.
So why are you here in Show--
I almost said Showtime.
Why are you here inGandang Gabi Vice?
We're here on a date.
- [CHEERING]- [VICE SQUEALING] Ohh!
That makes me happy.
Because usually,in Vice Comedy Club,
- many people date there.- That's true.
But I'm happy thatthere are also couples
dating here inGandang Gabi VIce.
Why? Why did you chooseto have a date in this program?
Because it's alsoour chance to see you live.
- Because...- Don't mention that.
You're pandering too much.You don't have to say that.
It's really difficultto get a slot here.
- Many people want to be here.- You need an in to be here.
So, if you don't havea connection,
then you can't geta slot to be here.
Verna's mom hasnever even been here.
Her mother's still outside,
selling peanuts to peopleat the audience entrance.
[VICE] How fun.
What's the best...
What's the best thingabout being in love?
For me, I think it's how I getto be with her every day.
[AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING] Ohh.
Back then, I was readyto just grow old alone.
- [VICE] Oh really?- Yes.
You were fine to be alonefor the rest of your life?
And that changed because of him?
Yes, he's been there sincethe very beginning.
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]- Yes!
That's great! How beautiful!
Doesn't it feel nice to wake upwhen you love someone?
Especially when the personyou love also loves you back.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Because not everyone who lovesis also loved back, right?
There are times whenit hurts because
you wonder why you'rethe only one giving love.
[AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
But when both of yougive love, it feels great.
You'd think that you're the mostblessed people in the world.
Do you always go on dates?
- Actually, yes.- Ah, really?
- Do you go to hotels?- [AUDIENCE CHUCKLES]
[VICE] Why don't yougo to hotels?
Oh, I-- I have a discount card.I'll lend it to you later.
- [LAUGHTER]- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Go ahead, use it. Becausethat's just one stamp left,
- I'll have free fried chicken.- [LAUGHTER]
Go ahead, you guys go first.
Yeah, there's-- The slippersthere are so extra.
One size seven, one size six.
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]- [LAUGHTER]
- You know it already?- The end is even cut off.
[VICE] Oh, Tetay knowsit so well!
- Oh, come on!- When was the last time
you broughtVerna there? [LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHTER]- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [UNINTELLIGIBLE]- It's so funny.
The ashtray is attached,and she keeps removing it.
I said, "Hey, it's supposedto be like that."
[VICE] Right?
So, I want your dayto be memorable tonight.
- Yes.- You know,
- Ion and I have this thing...- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Even if we don't go out much,
sometimes we have datesright at our home.
And we like to--
Do you dance together?
- Sometimes.- [VICE] You haven't-
Oh my, god!
You don't even have to bereally good at dancing.
But dancing togetherfeels so good.
Even in your room,in the bathroom, anywhere.
Where no one can see you.
Even when there's no music,
it feels likethere's music playing.
Come on, try it.
- Come here, you guys.- [VERNA, AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Just danceas if we're not...
as if we're not here.
Just play something nicefor them
and let yourself feel it.
Come on, feel it.
- [ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
Spin around.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
See? That feels so good.
[VICE] Especially when there'ssomeone live serenading you.
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALS]- Feel it.
- ["PALAGI" PLAYING]- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING, CLAPPING]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING, CLAPPING]
[AUDIENCE SQUEALS]
[AUDIENCE SINGING] Sa huli...
[AUDIENCE CHEERING, CLAPPING]
[AUDIENCE SQUEALING, CLAPPING]
[AUDIENCE CLAPPING]
- [AUDIENCE] Whoo!- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING, CLAPPING]
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING, CLAPPING]
[VICE] Gandang gabi, KZ and TJ!
Gandang gabi, Kapamilyaand Kapuso!
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]- [AUDIENCE CHANTING]
- Whoo!- [VICE] Aww.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Aww!
So, what? Am I the onewho's out of place?
- Oh.- [LAUGHTER]
[KZ] Sorry, sorry, sorry,sorry sorry, sorry,
- sorry.- You didn't even hug me
- when you saw me earlier.- [TJ LAUGHS]
- He cried.- Sorry, sorry.
- [VICE] Thank you very much!- [TJ] Thank you!
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]- My, god. How did it feel...
dancing with the loveof your life
while they were serenading you?
We're so blessed.
- I cried.- [VICE] Mhm.
So blessed. In case youdidn't know,
- I love them so much.- they're priests, pastors.
[LAUGHTER]
[ANNE RAY] I love them.And I love this one more.
- And then--- I thought I loved them more
- I got nervous.- And then!
Yeah, so you're a homewrecker.
Me, wrecking a home?!
[LAUGHTER]
Aww, you? How are you?
How did you--Because, of course,
women tend to be more emotionalabout things like that. But you?
- He doesn't have any emotions.- Um, actually...
It just reminded me of the nightof our wedding.
- Your wedding night? Why?- So, our first dance--
The caterer didn't show upon the night of your wedding?
- [RAM] They did. Thank, God.- Ah, they did.
Uh, it was just as fun too.
Is TJ and KZ's songpart of your love life?
- Yes, yes.- Yes.
- [VICE] Yeah.- That's the song from
when he walked down the aisle.
- [VICE] Aww.- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
You walked down the aislein a wedding gown?
- He also walked down the aisle.- Did you walk him down?
- [LAUGHTER]- [VICE] No, but
I'm so, so happyfor you guys.
Not everyone gets that chance,
gets that moment.
But you two, I'm justso happy for you.
- Let's give them both- Thank you.
- a round of applause.- [KZ] So deserved!
- Thank you.- Thank you for the chance.
You two, enjoy yourselves there.
We'll still be spending plentyof time
with your favorites.
This is my gift to youand to all of you.
- KZ and TJ.- [CHEERING]
- Thank you very much.- Thank you.
- That felt so good!- Very!
- It made me cry.- [KZ] Thank you, Vice.
It's like I just fellin love yesterday,
and the feeling is still fresh.
Like, yeah, it feelsso good to hear.
- It was beautiful.- [TJ] Is it my fault?
Right? Earlier,I was in brute mode.
I was just being a brute,but when I heard your song,
it made me soft.You have that effect.
- [TJ] Thank you, Vice.- [KZ] Yeah, thank you.
[VICE] It makes me soft.It makes me feel small. I felt--
- I felt like I was only 5'3- [KZ] It makes--
- and a half earlier.- It makes you small?
- [TJ LAUGHS]- It makes you-- When you're--
When you're soft, being smallmakes you look so pretty
because you're small,compared to a brute?
- That's okay. That's ladylike.- No, because when you said
it makes you feel small.Can this get any smaller, Vice?
- [VICE LAUGHS]- This is as small as I can get.
[VICE] Come on. When you see
- Thumbelina, you'll be proud- Look at the monitor,
- of yourself.- I'm cut off.
- [LAUGHTER]- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[LAUGHING] You got cut off.
That's why I adjusted, dear.
Look, these are the only shoes
- I wore.- Her shoes are so low today.
[VICE] Right? I'm just wearingkitten heels today.
[KZ] True.
- Mm.- [LAUGHTER]
It's like you're aboutto give me a medal.
Come on, I'm proud of you.
As my youngest,I'm proud of you.
Look at you. You're the only onewho survived
- the plane America sent to war.- Correct! Thank you so much!
- [VICE LAUGHS]- Wow, you're laughing.
[TJ LAUGHS] I expected this.
Well, why did you date someonewho flies a fighter jet?!
[LAUGHTER]
Who would say no to her, Vice?
- [VICE SCREAMS] Ohh!- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING, CLAPPING]
[AUDIENCE CHANTING]
You can't handle that!
- [VICE LAUGHS]- [AUDIENCE CHANTING]
The butterflies and great musicwon't stop tonight.
We'll also be filledwith insights
about what they're going through
in the dynamicsof their relationship.
Oh, that's why, no excuses,no sleeping just yet.
There's plenty of chit-chatcoming up when we return to
the most fun and most addictiveshow every Sunday night.
This is...
[ALL] Gandang Gabi, Vice!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Gandang gabi, KZ and TJ.
- Gandang gabi, Vice!- Gandang gabi, Vice.
Gandang gabi,Kapamilya and Kapuso!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING, CLAPPING]- [VICE LAUGHS]
You do it. Gandang gabi,Kapamilya and Kapuso!
Gandang gabi,Kapamilya and Kapuso!
[VICE] Yes! Are you comfortablewith your seat?
You might fall. You're alreadyat the edge,
- right at the end.- No, because they said
you should just chill.
So I tried doing this.Then, when I leaned back...
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
- You can't reach it anymore.- I can't reach it.
- I'll just do this.- [VICE LAUGHS]
With a chair like this,Vice, it's for a...
business-- It's for an interview
for jobs.
- A hearing.- So, I can't--
You can lie down on TJif you want.
- [VICE SCREAMING] Ohh!- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
This isn't your first timebeing on GGV together, right?
- [KZ] No.- How many years has it been
since you werelast on together?
- [KZ] Nine years ago.- [TJ] About nine years ago.
It's been so long.
- [VICE] Nine years ago.- [TJ] Nine years ago, yes.
You're not married yet.
- [TJ] We're not married yet.- Correct.
[VICE] Right? So whenI looked back on that video,
I said, "Oh, how cool!
They actually manifestedsomething here in this, um,
- this... this guesting."- [TJ] What was it?
- [TJ] What did we manifest?- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
Let's watch it.
- Let's go back to that moment.- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
What I thought about KZwhen I was courting her,
of course, was, hopefully,she'd be the last one.
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]- Because I'm her
very first, so I hopeshe'll be my last too.
[VICE] You too?
Of course, I hope so.
Because, of course, you wouldn'tenter a relationship
if you didn't seethe potential in that person
to be with youfor the rest of your life.
- So, hopefully.- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
We don't knowwhat will happen in the future,
but at least,
right in this moment,I see him as part of my future.
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]- [VICE] Ohh!
I thought what youmanifested there
was that you'd havea lot of condos to sell.
- Because of our styling before.- Right!
Look at how I looked there.
- [VICE] Oh, it's amazing.- Wow.
[VICE] You already claimed itat that moment.
- That we'd end up together--- That when-- after nine--
- Nine years?- [TJ] Nine years.
After nine years, the threeof us would meet
and you'd be marriedand still together.
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]- You're married too.
- [KZ, TJ] Ohh!- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
[VICE, TJ LAUGHING]
Right? It's fun.
A lot gets manifestedhere on GGV.
A lot of things come true.Even beauty queens
come here, and their wishescome true--
I really do give my blessing.
Yes, Madam Bertudis your godmother.
[LAUGHTER]
I'll grow taller,I'll grow taller.
Oh my goodness, that recordis going to be broken.
I might
I might just get youstilts tomorrow
so you can actuallymake that happen.
- [KZ] So I can grow taller.- Nine years ago...
As a married couple, howlong have you been married?
Six years married. Wewere dating for six years.
Two weeks ago, we celebratedour 6th anniversary.
Oh, wow!
How do you celebrate?
- We went to--- We guested in
- Yeng Constantino's concert.- [LAUGHter]
- [VICE] Ah, YES!- Yes, we were there.
After that,we flew to Japan.
We stayed therefor a couple of days.
Our favorite momentsis mostly us in Tokyo,
but we did the same thing.
We went ot ourfavorite restaurant--
- Was it cold in Japan?- No, it was hot.
- Why did you buy that then?- Yeah.
- It's cold in the studio.- [LAUGHTER]
- It's colder here- I'm getting goosebumps!
than in Japan.You're getting what?
I'm always here,but I don't get goosebumps.
I'm getting goosebumpsbecause it's too cold.
- [VICE CHUCKLES]- But it's cozy.
[VICE] So, six years.
How many people had youdated before dating each other?
KZ is my third girlfriend.
- [VICE] He was your first?- First and last.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- Wow.- Let's go!
Didn't he court youwhen you were a toddler?
You grew up with him.
[LAUGHTER]
You were 21 years oldwhen I courted you, right?
I think you courted mewhen you were 22
and then I was 23when we started dating.
Hey, you're beingso overdramatic.
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]- My gosh, she's so tight!
- [LAUGHTER]- What do you call each other?
Are you guys on a first-namebasis or you have your own
term of endearment.
Baby.
- Baby.- Baby.
And nowadays it's Love.
Yes, baby, love.But I prefer love.
[VICE] Why don't you wantto be called baby?
No, because sometimeswhen he says,
"Baby, you're so beautiful."or "Come here, baby."
He uses that endearmenton our dog too.
- [LAUGHTER]- So, I'm not sure it...
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]- Yeah, I say that to Fitz.
Is he really talkingto our dog, Fitz, or to me?
He says thing like,"Baby, you're so beautiful."
TJ, be honest,do you confuse them?
- [LAUGHTER]- I feel like.
It's because of this!
[LAUGHTER]
[TJ COOING, LAUGHS]
Oh no!
So that's why you changeyour hair color all the time!
You get her groomed, don't you?
- [LAUGHTER]- You're right. Just kidding.
Actually, I shared groomerswith all our dogs.
[VICE LAUGHS]
Don't be surprisedif you see her
- [KZ] Barking.- eating on the floor like this.
[TJ CHUCKLES]
- Like that.- But he calls me love.
- I prefer being called Love.- [VICE] Love.
What about you and Ion?
- Babe.- Babe.
- "Good morning, babe."- Your eyes are sparkling.
- Right!- When you ask about Ion.
My eyes has veneers.
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[TF] Seriously.
But seriously, if you ask people about the person they love,
- their eyes sparkle.- Their eyes sparkle.
- Yes.- Like the world is filtered.
Everything around youlooks even more beautiful.
And when you're in love,hearing love songs
is the best feeling ever.
But why didyou get married twice?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- On our first wedding--- Was the priest a scam?
No! [CHUCKLES]
Our first weddingwas during the pandemic.
So, KZ and I...
we were dating forthree or four years.
We were dating for five years.
We lived in separate houses,
so we wanted to live togetherduring the pandemic.
And for us, for that to happen, we wanted to get married first.
You didn't want to live togetherwithout getting married.
Yes, that'swhat we decided on.
At that time,we asked our parents
if we could do that,because I was living alone and
she was living with her housemaid and sister in her condo.
So we asked ifwe could get married.
That was the plan,but when we opened up
they suggested thatwe should get married,
because according to themif there's a time
that you should be together
it's this.
The world is uncertain, and youshould be there for each other.
but you should be sureand together for each other.
The catch was thather parents weren't there.
They were in Mindanao, andno flights were going here.
It's selfless of them
to agree to let us get marriedwithout both our parents,
and we're both the eldest kids,
so they didn't experienceany weddings.
They didn't ask you to waitfor them to get there
or to wait for the pandemicto pass?
- [KZ] No, they didn't.- They agreed.
They were ona zoom call but
they were alsowearing formal clothes.
Oh, so they were all crazy.
- [LAUGHTER]- No!
- Just so they can be involved.- They wore that to be involved!
- They were called through Zoom.- Yeah!
- They changed their shirts.- They're working from home.
no, but they reallyput in effort there.
It really was!They weren't in there in person
but you're wearingformal clothes.
- [TJ] It's true.- They're crazy!
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]- That's crazy!
There was a TV next to usboth our families were there.
So, we said to ourselves,
after three years-- on ourthird wedding anniversary,
we'll give it back to them.
So, for our third anniversary,its more for our parents
The theme is mostly about them.
For the vows forour second wedding,
my vows are for her parents,
and her vows are for my parents.
So, that's what happened.
That's great, isn't it?
The pandemic was unexpected
but when you look back,it's like you planned
it in your head whatyou wanted to happen.
And you fulfilled it.It's even in your vows.
Your inner selvesare completely whole.
Correct. True.
When everything wasn't sure,especially with the pandemic,
it was like God's hands werereally on top of everything.
He was orchestratingthings as if he were saying,
"It's okay. Everythingwill make sense in the end."
And now we realizedthat, yeah...
This was really meant to happen.
Who said to have a secondwedding so everyone's present?
Whose idea was it?
I think it wasa mutual decision.
You thought of itat the same time like, "Ah!
- Let's have a second wedding!"- [LAUGHTER]
- I think it was right after- Mutual. [CHUCKLES]
our first wedding, when weboth saw our parents
dressed formallyand on a Zoom call,
and right after the ceremonythe call ended,
It hurts my heartto know that as parents,
they didn't getto have their moment
to see their kids get married.We're both the eldest--
They didn't get to walk usdown the aisle or even see us.
Because that moment was robbed from them during the pandemic,
we decided thatsince our parents
never asked usfor anything grand,
we knew that even if itwas just an intimate wedding,
they'd be really happyas long as
we give them that moment wherethey walk us down the aisle.
Yes, their weddingwas so simple.
our prepared food/spread wasjust bopis and dinengdeng.
Correct.That's so true.
It's just peanut,and you pass it around.
[LAUGHTER]
You just gave your guestsnoodles and liver spread.
You're absolutely right.
- That's all.- Mm-hmm.
That's fun.
- You achieved it together.- Mm-hmm.
Right?
So, on your first-- you saidyou weren't living together,
then you lived togetherafter the first wedding.
[KZ] Correct.
What's so special aboutyour first wedding?
When you were togetherfor the first time,
what's so specialabout the first night
that made you realize, ah,we're finally living together?
What's so specialabout that night?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Is there something like that?
When nighttime came,did you dance together?
- Was music playing?- We really did dance.
[LAUGHTER]
Did you light a candleand something caught on fire,
then you got sued for it?
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
They say that you're extremelytired after the wedding,
As they say, nothingwill happen after the wedding.
[LAUGHTER]
It depends on whetheryou're not horny.
- But if you're--- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Here's what happened.
[LAUGHTER]
[SINGING] Here we go.
Here's what happened.
So, here's what happened.
We said that--
Why are you reacting that way?I'm already married!
[SILLY SFX,LAUGH TRACK PLAYING]
Go ahead. You rarely talkabout things like this.
[LAUGHTER]
I always talk about embarrassingthings like this.
You know this, Meme!
He's always been the good boywho hasn't done anything bad.
- Not a single bad trait!- Yeah!
I don't haveanything good to offer!
But that nightI wasn't a good boy.
- Oh!- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey!Our parents will watch this!
[VICE LAUGHS]
You told me to tell them!
[VICE] You weren'ta good boy! What did he do?
- Wow.- That night
you weren't a good boy!
Did he put underwearin your mouth?
- [LAUGHTER]- He locked me out.
He put a brief in your mouth,and he bit off your bra.
- [LAUGHTER]- [GROWLS]
This is your end! [GROWLS]
Hey, that's crazy!
We said, " Wow. Wewaited for this for five years."
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]- [VICE] Wow.
You've got the wholenight to yourselves.
The urge to be togetheris so strong that night!
I told him, "Love, I don't thinkI can do this tonight.
Then he said, "Yeah,you're right." And then--
Oh no, it's becoming too visual!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]- [SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wait, so you prepared!
- We didn't do it the next day!- [LAUGHTER]
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, you didn't waittill the next day!
- I said, alright--- Mommy, Daddy,
please let's turn on the TV.
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]- [TJ] I said...
let's just do it tomorrow.
And then,after a few minutes,
tomorrow is too long.
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, your branding changed.
[VICE LAUGHS]
He matched thebranding of the show.
He left his old branding.
Correct, he changedhis branding.
Maybe next concert youwon't have a shirt on.
[LAUGHTER]
Then...
his front acts are Masculadosand Viva Hot Babes.
Yeah, that's it.
So, who initiated it?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
So, it was you!
It wasn't voluntary.
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you meanI did it voluntarily?
I don't know anything!
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]- Ah...
Ah, you were a virgin.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]- [SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, you don't haveto broadcast it!
Yes, whatever.I was a virgin.
- [VICE] He was your first?- I'm getting stressed.
- So he's your first boyfriend?- Your first boyfriend.
Yes so everything--
- I'm having a panic attack.- [LAUGHTER]
So, all that I know
- came from him.- Oh, that's crazy!
You're not just a composerbut also a mentor!
[LAUGHTER]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Mentor! That's crazy!
This is a crazy topic.
Vince, you shouldbe friends with him!
I'll get your number later.Seriously.
- We have a guru here.- Yeah.
So that's it, thank you. Ah!
Question. Okay.
- Your face!- You're amazing, because
that was your first time.
You knew that's going to happenbecause you'll get married
and you'll livein a house together.
How stressful was itfor a girl like you,
who had never experienced it?
How stressful was it?
Was it stressful?Was it exciting?
How did you prepare?
Were you nervous or excited?
How many timesdid you take a shower?
Did you use a feminine washto gargle?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING, SCREAMING]
What did you do that time?
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]- Whoo!
They're going crazy.Oh my god. My god. My god.
All of you are over18 years old, right?
Is that right?
This episode will be rated withvery strong parental guidance.
- Ah, okay, okay, okay!- It will air at 10:30 PM.
Just put a bleep on it, in case!
- Ah, uhm...- How stressful?
- Was it stressful?- Oh, at first, it was.
Because, of course,it's stressful,
but of course, I'm also excitedfor it to happen because--
sis! You know a cabinet thathasn't been opened for a while,
and once you do, boom!
[LAUGHTER]
It's like an openinga door with an old hinge!
When you open it,there'd be creaking.
- Oh my god!- The sound's like
in horror moviesbecause the hinge is old!
It's not smooth, it's squeaky!
It sounds like "eek, eek, eek!"
[LAUGHTER]
It's stressful in a way,because it's my first time and
as a woman-- wow, overacting!
I felt like I don't wantour first time
to be a bad experiencefor the both of us.
Something like that. But I'mthankful because TJ, he was...
He was gentlewhen it mattered.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]- And...
- You're nothing!- [KZ] He was gentle
- when he had to!- You said you weren't
a good boy!You turned out to be gentle!
- No, here me out.- He said,
in the beginning.
No, no, it was incomplete!
He was gentle when he had toand rough when he did.
Ah! Just kidding, just kidding.
- Just kidding!- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- Just kidding! Just kidding!- [VICE LAUGHING]
- Aaah!- Oh my god, guys!
You can't handle that!
[VICE LAUGHS]And that's pretty good, too.
I want to make thata caption for my reels.
What did you say again?
[KZ SNORES]
He was gentle-- what was it?
I'm cannot repeat it.Actually, it's not right...
But she said,he was gentle-- what?
[VERNA] When he had to,
and rough when he did.
It should've been"and rough when he needed to."
[KZ, VICE] Aah!
Oh, now you're stopping me?
You did it first!
[VICE] Slay!
But mother, admit it...
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING, SCREAMING]
But you said something earlier,you said,
of course,you wanted to make sure
it was going to be memorableand enjoyable for both of you.
- So...- [TJ] This is too much!
- You studied?- Wait, is this body one?
- This is already body two.- This is body two.
Body one is wherethe sweet moments are.
Sweet. So, you studied,watched, researched?
- Actually, I don't know.- I don't know this.
- Did you do any research?- No. Ah!
Because other people,especially when,
what's it called? The bride'sparty before the wedding?
- What's it called?- Bridal shower.
Others, they watch.
And for some, their friendstell them what to do.
I didn't have a bridal shower.
Ah, because of the pandemic?
Yes, that's one reason.And then, because
- we were close friends,- And there's no water?
- Right. Then,- [VICE LAUGHS]
since we were close friends,
we have thesame circle of friends.
And I didn't have a lotof female friends.
So, if I had a bridal shower,
there'd only be two,three people there.
So, it never happened.
But I trust him.
- How many times did you shower?- Before?
Sometimes, you'll frequentthe bathroom
because of how stressed you are.
Yes! And I'd pretend that I'mdoing something in the bathroom,
but in reality, there's none.
You're pretending to be busy!
You don't know ifyou'll lie down.
I arrangedthe slippers a few times.
We're not even using it.
- [VICE LAUGHS]- That's why I waited too long!
Why? Isn't it worth it?
- [VICE] Ah!- [LAUGHTER]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING] KZ! KZ! KZ!
- Gosh, is this still right?- Seriously.
KZ is ready to fight tonight!
[TJ] Are we doingthe right thing?
This one even asked us earlier,
"Do you have anything thatyou don't wanna talk about?"
Ah! Now, she'sasking us everything!
[LAUGHTER]
I was just listening.
I'm not prompting that much!
But, she... [LAUGHS]
You're generous tonight, huh.
- [KZ] Right!- You love me so much, right?
- You love GGV so much?- And I'm...
I'm like you. I'm not afraidto tell stories.
That's me, that's us.
- That's normal! We're married!- They're married, hello?
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]- My gosh.
Do it when you getmarried. If not, then...
And also,
it's part of marriage.
Correct.
How about you?For her, there was stress,
she doesn't know what to do.
[KZ] This guyis already an expert!
- You know when--- [LAUGHTER]
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
-She judges you too much, right?- Too much! [LAUGHS]
But how was it? Was it stressful
knowing that this isyour partner's first time?
That she might be scared?
How did you take care of her
and how did you take careof that moment?
Of course, initially,I'm excited.
But...
She was right.I was gentle at first.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]- Slowly.
What's it then? Did youtalk to each other first?
We talked to each otherat first, as prep. [LAUGHS]
- There was a preamble.- Then,
when you're in the moment,
you'll be the ones to-- [LAUGHS]
With TJ, if there arethings happening,
he'll ask,
"Are you comfortable or do youwant to do it another time?
- There was that.- Oh, like that.
Are you comfortable? Do youwant to do it another way?
On the side? How about this?
Let's try this.
There are a lot of options.
He was very mindful of me.
But, it all startedwith a very sweet kiss.
When you're just talkingto each other.
Even just a kiss on theforehead. As simple as that.
It starts with a stare.
- Ah, with the stare.- Just a stare.
- You look like a mugger.- Ah, it starts with a stare.
You did it on the stairs?
[LAUGHTER]
Stair!
- Starts with a stare.- With Verna, there's no prep.
- [DIVINE] None.- Right away.
- [TJ] Oh!- Did you get married?
Yes! A civil wedding.
Ah...
Even at home, your partneris only civil with you, right?
- You don't talk that much?- [LAUGHTER]
- He's affectionate!- He puts
her dinner on the floor.
But we'll get married again.
- Ah, really?- Yes.
What's your cult?You've got a cult, right?
My dream is to get marriedon a cliff.
- [TJ] Wow!- Then you'll push each other?
[KZ] So when someone says no,you just push them.
[VICE LAUGHS] Slay!
Okay. Since you're a singer,
if you'll describe TJ's pet,
for singers, what do you callsopranos, altos? Is it range?
Voice?
I don't know the technical term.
What is it called, sir?
- Voice?- Vocal range?
You're rude! You're beingvocal in front of me!
- Vocal!- Yes!
Vocal range.
The highest range is soprano,
is that the highest?
There are many different typesof soprano.
Soprano, alto.
- Yes.- Soprano one, soprano two.
- Alto, also base and tenor.- That's right.
When you sang,what was your range?
Soprano, alto, base, or tenor?
Nothing can be heard!
Because of how high it was,
only the dogswere able to hear it.
[KZ SQUEAKING] Just kidding!
[LAUGHTER]
Let's talk about something else.
Are you performingon ASAP together or not?
- [KZ] Rarely.- [TJ] The one in Australia.
The recent one.
Oh, only on special episodes.
You have been performingin ASAP for a long time now.
- Right?- Yes, yes.
How was it?What's the best part--
What is your memorableexperience in ASAP?
The recent one, in Sydney.
Our last performance.Because we performed there,
it was just the two of us.
We also performed ourperformances in In Between.
Oh! You showed a sneak peekof your concert tour.
But I heard a gossip.
- [TJ Wha's that?- Yes.
They're talking about you in theASAP dressing room last time.
- What did you do?- I'm getting nervous!
You-you left somethingon the stage.
Huh? Was that me?
Oh, it was KZ!
- Me?- Let's start over.
They're talking about you twoon the ASAP dressing room.
One of you seems to have left
- something on the ASAP stage.- Oh my god.
Who was the one who leftsomething on the ASAP stage?
- Hey!- Are we telling the story?
We're telling--
We're telling it?
Just write it down,I'll post it on Facebook.
Who was the one who leftsomething on the ASAP stage?
It's not on the stage, Vice.
- Where?- But,
still inside the studio.
But it was his fault.
- Why?- Because...
Eeeh, how are wegoing to tell it
without thewhole episode getting
- bleeped out?- This was a long time ago!
- We're still newlyweds.- It was a long time ago.
It was during the pandemic.
Then, during the pandemic,
the tech team cannothand us the microphone.
- You'll get your own.- So there's a table,
containing little basketswith names on it.
It has your in-ear, yourmicrophone, and other things.
And then, [KZ VOCALIZES]
we did the opening performance.
All artists were therefor the opening performance.
All the artists were there,Sir Gary, Sir Martin.
All of them.
At the end of the show,
you're going to put yourmicrophones back in the baskets.
Sis! When I checked my pocket,
Your microphonewas in your pocket?
- No, the in-ear.- Ah, the in-ear.
My ear pack was in my pocket.
Move back, dear,you're blocking my camera.
- [LAUGHTER]- Sorry!
What a celebrity!
Very mindful of the shot.
Because this is the director'sonly option for the shot!
Okay, moving on!
And then,
when I checked my pocket,
I was in the middle andall the artists were there
giving back their microphones,
When I pulled my in-earfrom my pocket,
something came with it!
- From your pocket?- From my pocket.
Something came with it.What was it?
- [TJ LAUGHING]- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- The, uh...- Oh my god.
T-th-the...
The packet of the...
The sachet! [LAUGHS]
The packet where it came from.There's nothing inside!
- Only the packet!- The packet of trust!
- The packet of...- The packet of trust!
- Yes, that!- The packet of trust!
The packet of trust! Correct!
- When I picked it up...- Cherry-flavored!
When I picked it up...
I really felt the air at ASAPchange like whoosh!
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
- I was frozen!- [VICE] Did someone see you?
I'm sure. I'm surethey all saw me
but didn't react because I feltthem go [GASPS].
[LAUGHTER]
So of course I couldn't lookat them because I was stunned!
I was shook to my bones!
- I froze like this. [GASPS]- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICE] Apparently,Sir Gary Valenciano saw you.
-So that's why he prayed for me.- [VICE] He picked it up.
- And prayed over it.- [LAUGHTER]
[KZ] It was really crazy.When I got home I told him,
"It's all your fault!"
I saw it fell so I plannedto throw it to the trash
while on the way outbefore ASAP.
- I just forgot all about it.- She put it in her pocket.
I put it in my pocket.
I just prayed that Sir Martinand Sir Gary didn't see it.
- And then... [LAUGHS]- They're judging me for sure!
Then she told me,"Babe, it was crazy."
She told me everythingand said, "They saw everything!
I hope they'll thinkit was just a sachet
- of instant noodles.- of instant noodles."
- [LAUGHTER]- [VICE] That big?!
- Sachet of the seasoning!- [LAUGHING]
- The seasoning pack.- [VICE] But I have a question.
Why do you have it and not him?
- Because...- Oh, you wear it?
- [KZ] No!- [LAUGHTER]
- [VICE] On your foot.- On my foot!
No but, maybe when he cleanedstuff, maybe it fell somewhere.
So I saw it when I went out...
- On her way to ASAP.- Yes.
So she picked it upto throw it out.
[VICE] But you found itat your house, not the studio?
At our house.
If I saw it at the studio,just who does it belong to?
- [VICE LAUGHS]- [LAUGH TRACK]
- So--- Who knows?
You guys could use itat the studio too.
- [TJ] It's at our house.- [KZ] That's crazy.
She picked it up to throw it outbut she put it in her pocket.
[VICE] Oh, so...
that's what you guys practice?
- To, you know.- [KZ] Correct.
Just because you're alreadymarried
doesn't mean that, you know?
- And at that time--- Others use it
when they don't planon having kids yet.
Right? So that's your practice.
It's always, uh...
When you ask...there are couples
who get uncomfortabletalking about these things.
Especially in the Philippines,it's usually asked,
"How long have you twobeen together?
When are you getting a child?"Stuff like that.
For you two, when youget asked questions about it,
because you've been marriedfor a long time now.
- [TJ] Six years.- For sure there are a lot
- of people pestering you.- Always.
How do you deal with them?
Hmm... There's a loton Facebook. [CHUCKLES]
- That's right.- [VICE] On Facebook?
A lot of people askin the comments section--
Yeah. It's like you can't bea woman
if you don't have children.
Personally, well, for me and TJ,
he's the one who's readyto be a father.
Ever since, he's the onewho opens up
and says that he's readyto be a father, but...
it's more on my side, where I'mat the stage where...
there are still a lot of thingsI want to do in my career,
things I want to buildfor myself
as a person, as a woman.
I want to make surethat I'm not a baby
taking care of a baby.
- I even saw a--- [VICE] Oh, that's wonderful.
"That I'm no longer a babytaking care of a baby."
I owe that to my childthat I know...
I will never be readyto become a parent
but I also thinkit's my responsibility
to at least try to be ready.
- Yes.- [KZ] For the--
It's not even a matter of--
because when we get toldthings like
oh we have money,our shows sold out,
but it doesn't just endwith that.
- Yeah.- [KZ] It's not just about that.
It's a lifetime responsibility.
I don't want to just have kids
because I was pressuredinto becoming a mom.
I don't want to become a mother
just to have someoneto take care of me
when I grow old.
What I always pray for,
especially when TJ and Ialways talk about it,
we had a really long and hardconversation about it and...
I really told him. I was honestwith him.
- I told him I'm not yet ready.- [VICE] Mm-hmm.
That I still have thingsI want to do.
And that I don't wantto be unfair to him,
I don't want to be unfairto our future children.
When I become a mother,I want to be focused on my kids.
- [AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]- So, I told--
Oh, thank you, guys.
I really told him that.
And again, I wanna be a mombecause I wanna be a mom.
- [VICE] Yeah.- So...
At that time, it was alsoa struggle to me.
Because I know that as a wife,it's like...
I can give thatto my husband, but um...
as a mom,
I also had a very longconversation with God.
I told Him, "Lord...
to be honest with you,you know what is in my heart
but, to be honest with you,
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I-- I'm not saying I don't wantto be a mom
but I'm not yet readyto be a mom.
But Lord, if it is your willfor me to become one,
then plant that love in meto become a mom.
Help me nurture that love to become a mom
- until it really...- [AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
really grows into somethingmore than myself
where I can be certain thatI'm ready to love my child."
- Yeah.- [KZ] Hmm.
And, you're not just beingsensible.
You're being reasonableand sensible
as a womanand as a future parent.
And every child deservesthat kind of a parent.
- [KZ] Aw, thank you.- Right?
- [AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]- [VICE] Because,
for a lot of people, it is easyto bear children.
- Correct.- But to stand by it
and provide a decent lifefor that child demands a lot.
In the Philippines,especially... for us...
'Cause I've experiencedthat before.
In the...
In poverty-stricken communitiesand families, it's like...
This is back then,I'm not sure now.
But back then, we were madeto believe
that love and familywere the only two things
important in life.
Until you realize that lovingone another isn't enough.
That staying togetherwith your family isn't enough.
Right?
There are other things you need.
There are other things you needin order to live
and at least leada decent way of living.
And that takes a lotof responsibility and...
it must've felt so nicefor KZ that...
there's a man who is willingto listen to her
and accept the principlesshe believes in.
That I felt comfortableto be honest with you
is amazing.
How were you
when you were told,"I'm not yet ready.
It will come but not now."
Well, KZ told me that...
I-- We believe
that the responsibilityof becoming a parent
doesn't start only whenthe child is born.
The responsibility starts now.
Even if you're nota parent just yet,
it is in your responsibilityto prepare everything
before the child is born.
So-- And I always believed
that it is a mutual decisionbetween a couple.
The decision can't be minealone.
Because we're both parents.
So if she saysthat she's not ready,
then so be it.
Because it doesn't workthat way.
Just because I'm the mandoesn't mean I get to decide.
It's two of us. She's the onecarrying the child, so.
- Yeah.- [VICE] But is it difficult
for you as the partnerwho's ready to be a father?
You're ready and you wantto become one.
But your partner isn'tand you respect that.
Still, you want to. Like,you respect them but still.
- [TJ] Yes.- Is it hard for you?
- [TJ] Of course--- At the start, was it painful
and you just triedto understand it?
Well, as a couple you haveto have...
those... first of all, you haveto have those conversations.
It is important for you twoto be able to talk about
the hard questions.All those things.
You can't just leave themhanging in the air.
So, we have to havethose conversations.
And when we talked about it,
it's like... [CLICKS TONGUE]um...
First and foremost, I believe...
I want to have a child,of course.
Now, KZ isn't sayingher heart's against it.
She's not saying that we'renever having a child.
But I also believe that a coupleis a family.
And for me, the two of usis already enough.
- [VICE] Mm-hmm.- So,
if we are to have a childin the future,
then that's a blessing.
But, if it's just the two of us,
then I'm very much happywith my life
- right now with my wife.- [VICE] Hmm.
- [AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]- [VICE] That's beautiful.
And what you said about how...
if you are to have a childtogether is a bonus,
- [TJ] Mm-hmm.- but having a child with you
is not the reasonwhy I'm with you.
- Correct, exactly.- Exactly, exactly.
I'm with you because I love you.
- Whether we have a kid or not.- [KZ] Mm-hmm.
And I'm grateful because healso acknowledges that...
when a woman decidesto become a mom it's not just...
it doesn't endafter nine months.
- [VICE] Yes.- Of carrying the baby.
Actually, in those nine months,just think about it.
Even getting a headache for day
makes you want to drinktons of medicine.
You even take a sick leavefrom work, right?
So imagine what a womangoes through
when a woman decidesto become a mom.
And that doesn't end there.
A woman's beingliterally changes
- when she decides to be a mom.- Forever.
Like...
I'm grateful because he alsotries to educate himself.
What could possibly happen?Like,
there are a lot of womenwho give birth
who couldn't see their childrenafter doing so.
Something happens along the wayand that's part of the journey.
So I'm at the stage where...
Allow me to be prepared.
- [VICE] Yeah.- Because I'll go through it.
I'm gratefulbecause he understands.
Like, "Yeah, I'm here for youno matter what it takes
to help you get there.
I'll be there but I'm not justpushing you to get there.
I'm gonna be with youby your side."
The last time we talked togetherwas two weeks ago, right?
We agreed that if ever,
since the topicwas brought up again,
if ever you decidedthat you're ready
and we're going to do it,
we first have to make surethat you're okay.
- First and foremost.- Physically?
Physically. That's the firststep. If she's really ready.
Because though we want it,she's my priority.
If the doctor says it's okay,then we'll go for it.
[VICE] When we were talkingabout it earlier,
you're getting teary-eyed.
What were you feelingat that moment?
Were you emotionalbecause you understand her
or were you emotionalbecause at that time,
you further realize
just how much you love your wifewhile we were talking.
[TJ] The latter.
Because I want to...
Of course, as a man,it's natural
to want to have a baby, but...
My love for her prevails.
So, like, she's the reason...
For me, she's the reasonwhy I live.
- [VICE] Yeah.- So...
yeah. [CHUCKLES]
[HEARTWARMING MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop crying.You're making me cry too.
[VICE] How would you feelif you have a baby
and once it gets born,this is what it's wearing.
- [LAUGHTER]- [SILLY SFX]
Hi, baby!
[IMITATING BABY CRYINGWHILE SINGING]
It comes out swinging, huh?[IMITATING CONTINUES]
[LAUGHING]
I'm excited if that ever happensbut then again--
[KZ] Will you bea godmother, Vice?
Sure.
- I would love to.- [KZ] Aw! Alright!
- [LAUGHS] Alright!
Thank you.
I would love to.I would love to...
to witness youexpanding your family.
And I would love to...It feels so good
if you chose meto help raise the child.
- Aw, when we get there.- Yeah.
When we get there.
- And then...- Now I'm crying.
Of course, you love TJso much.
You love TJ.
And while loving him,you're loving yourself, too.
And when we love someone,
we want that personto be happy.
As much as we can,
we'll give them what makesthem happy.
Does it ever make you sadsomehow, sometimes,
thinking, "He might want it,but I'm not ready yet"?
That kind of thing...
Because some peoplefeel guilty
when they can't givetheir partner what they want,
sometimes to the point of givingin just to make them happy.
Yes, of course,especially at first.
Yeah, when we first talkedabout it,
I really apologized,knowing how much he wanted it.
But I also knew
he wouldn't be happyif I wasn't 100 percent in.
So, I really had to be...
I really had to be honest,
because I don't thinkwe would both be happy if...
if I didn't tell himhow I felt.
And I don't thinkwe'd be fully happy
unless we met in the middle
in making the biggest decisionof our lives,
because it's goingto change our lives forever.
Yeah. And you would know...
if you're genuinely lovedby the person,
if they don't make youfeel guilty
for loving yourselfbefore loving them.
[KZ] Correct.
Right? They won't let youfeel guilty
for loving yourself firstbefore them.
They'll let you be...
"It's okay if you loveyourself before me."
Because, after all,
you can't givefrom an empty cup,
so love yourself first
so you can properly loveyour future children.
What is going on?How did our chat go from earlier
to ending up here? And...
Well, our show is late,
and we've been talkingfor so long.
It's already 9:30 AMon Magandang Buhay.
[KZ] Correct.
They'll reportthe traffic soon.
But I'm gratefulyou asked me that,
because a lot of peoplerefuse to talk about it,
and I understand why.
But I also thinktalking about it
makes other women facingthe same thing feel seen,
knowing they aren't alonein what they're going through.
So, even thoughit's hard for me,
if it helps others knowthat someone understands them,
then I'm fine with it.
And having someonespeak for them, right?
Earlier, I asked them first
because I wanted to discuss it,
since I felt it wasreally relevant and relatable.
But I felt I neededto ask permission first,
because I didn't want herto feel uncomfortable.
- So I said...- Thank you.
"Are you okay with talkingabout that, or not?
Is there anythingyou don't want to talk about?"
TJ said, "I'm okay with it.How about you?"
KZ said, "Yeah.Sure, let's talk about it."
Because, you know...
- You're not speaking for your--- And we trust you.
Thank you.Thank you for your trust.
- [EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]- [CLAPPING]
And hearing you talk about it,
we're not just hearingKZ's story,
- we're hearing so...- Yes.
the story of so many womenright now.
Right? You're speakingfor them?
[TETAY] Aww.
Verna, why are you gettingemotional?
If you're not ready yet, KZ...
well, I can be a babymaker.
[LAUGHTER]
I'm free every Wednesday.
[LAUGHING] I don't knowwhat's going on.
Would you let her beyour surrogate mother?
[LAUGHING]
My genes are strong, though.
Her jeans are strong,look how dirty her denim is!
Vince, what did you realize
while TJ was talkingabout these things?
What I realized was...
about being responsiblewhen it comes to parenting.
And I saw...it also made me think...
I'm so blessed my parentsprepared for me,
and I guess my dreamfor my future child
is not just to give themwhat my parents gave me,
but to top it.
- Exactly.- Exactly.
- Yes.- Nice.
[CLAPPING]
So far, his parentingis going well.
[LAUGHTER]
Tetay, how does it feel
that Vince appreciateshow you raised him?
I don't know, he brings homea girlfriend, and now this?
No, you guys sound wonderful.
I mean, like, listening to KZand TJ talk about having kids.
Because after I gave birthto my second baby...
Sorry, sorry, I'm drinkingalcohol here.
Gosh, some people struggleso much to conceive...
and then give birth.
Tetay just uses Dulcolax,right?
You can give birth like that?
How many times did you visitthe OB because of Dulcolax?
Yes. The doctor told meto wear a diaper.
[LAUGHTER]
You guys sound wonderful.It's so joyful.
We're learning so many lessons.
Verna, please, I'll tell youwhen to open your mouth.
[LAUGHTER]
- Oh my god.- Gosh.
We're talking here,no monkey business for now.
[LAUGHS]
I told you guys to play cards,not act like monkeys.
This is...
So beautiful. So wonderful.
I mean, my knowledge ofKZ Tandingan was surface-level,
but now I've gotten toknow her deeper, you know?
Same with Sir TJ...and with you, too.
I mean, I feel...
I'm so blessed to be partof this show.
I feel like when I go homelater...
"Babe, I think we're goingto have a third baby."
[LAUGHTER]
- Wow.- It's wonderful to hear.
We usually just fool around,you know?
We share a lot of importantthings to a lot of people.
- It's so nice, in fairness. KZ.- Yes.
It's really something elsetalking to TJ and KZ.
Especially when she raps.
- Like KZ Mil (Ez Mil)? KZ Mil.- [TETAY] KZ Mil.
Since we talked aboutyour plans
of having a baby in the future.
Not yet, but in the future.
Don't you writea lot of songs?
I was thinking about writing...
You know how some songwritersmake songs
for their future baby
or for their newborn?
Do you ever think about that?
I've already written one.
- Ah...- You already made one?
I've already made one.
Did anyone here watchSarili Nating Mundo Day 2?
[AUDIENCE] Yes!
There, at the Araneta concertlast year,
you were there.But on day two,
I shared a song with everyoneat the Araneta
that I wrotefor our future baby.
Can we hear a bit of it?
Sure, can I borrowmy guitar for a moment?
It's better if...
Where is the guitar?
Tetay, the guitar! Have somerespect for our guests!
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]- It's Verna's fault!
Verna made the one with goutwalk all the way here!
She's already struggling.
[VERNA] Sorry, sorry, sorry.Wow!
What did he say?What did he say?
"I'll do it, I feel badfor you."
- [MAN] Wow!- [ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- Thank you, bro.- Sparks are flying.
You like that, huh?
So, what's the title?
- Aurora.- Aurora.
Because there was a time...we went to Canada,
and I arrived in Canada first.
I had a chance to seethe Aurora Borealis.
Everyone went, but I chosenot to go.
- It sounds super cheesy, but...- Why?
I wanted to be with herwhen I...
Ah!That's also my dream with Ion,
to see the Aurora Borealis.
He always shows methat picture.
- Yes.- I hope we get the chance
to see it.
And then eventually,we saw the Aurora Borealis.
I wrote a song about it.So, I was at home,
writing a song aboutthe Borealis.
I really wantedto see the Borealis.
I'll wait for the perfect timeto see you.
I can't wait to see you.
And then, songwriting happenedto me.
The song grew on me, and thenI realized, "Wait a minute."
This isn't aboutthe Aurora Borealis anymore.
Because when I become afather, I want to be a girl dad.
- So, a girl.- Oh, really?
- A girl.- And does he tell you that?
He wants a girl.How about you?
I just want to bea mom to your children.
[VICE GANDA] Aww...
So when I said if wehave a baby and it's a girl,
we're going to name herAurora.
So that's the titleof the song.
[GUITAR STRUMMING]
[SINGING]Aurora
I will wait for you
May not be now, but soon
As you dance to my tune
Aurora
I'd give my all for you
Let your colors bloom
Give you up my moon
I can't wait to see
The wonder of your beauty
A tapestry painted in majesty
Your melody (I know)
Will forever capture me
Aurora
I will wait for you
- [VICE GANDA] Aww...- [CLAPPING]
It's so beautiful.
[SINGING] Aurora...
I'll always find my way back--
- [LAUGHTER]- [KZ] ...to your arms.
[TETAY] Look at Verna!
- [VERNA] It made me cry.- So lovely. It made me cry.
It's really so nicelistening to you guys.
And you sang harmonyso softly.
- She already knows the song.- I was crying when...
...the first time he sang itfor me.
- Yeah, I remember that.- Yeah, I really cried.
- Did you have a breakdown?- Yeah.
I'd probably break down too
if Ion played the guitarand sang to me.
- [TJ LAUGHS] Why? Why?- Once you hear him...
- If that's Ion...- [TJ] Doesn't he like singing?
- [SINGING] Haurora...- [TETAY] Hey!
- [TJ LAUGHS] Wow, you're harsh.- All H's. Just the letter H.
[TETAY]You're so harsh on him.
He said he wants to seethe Haurora Borealis.
[CHUCKLING]
Where is that? In Tarlac?In Concepcion.
In Concepcion,there's a Haurora Borealis.
- [TETAY] You're so harsh.- [LAUGHING]
When do you planto see the Aurora Borealis?
You know, we don't plananymore,
because we don't wantto be disappointed,
since so many of our plansdidn't push through.
[KZ] And with our typeof work--
And with our line of work,especially yours,
everything is always plannedand all.
So sometimes, when you dothose kinds of things with Ion,
it brings back the excitementof the unknown, right?
That's why I just listened whenyou were talking earlier.
Because our storyis kind of similar.
There are things I wantto give him that he wants,
but there are other thingsI still want to do.
- Mm.- Which...
of course isn't easy, right?
- You have to explain it to him.- Correct.
Because if you don't align,you won't understand each other.
And sometimes, when thoseconversations aren't...
Like...Like if they're not given
a moment to reallybe talked about,
those things can makeor break relationships.
- [VICE GANDA] True.- Right?
- So... Correct.- It really takes compromise.
Both of you have to agreeon what's happening.
- Correct.- It can't be just one person.
There can't be a bossin a relationship.
- [TJ] Yes. That's true.- [KZ] Correct. Correct.
And there has to be respect,really.
- True.- Respect for each other.
And like Ion understands,for example,
he understands the demandsof your job.
Like the demand of beingVice Ganda.
Like all the thingsyou have to set aside
when you decide to goto that next step
or take that next step,like that.
TJ is like that, too.He acknowledges that,
"Wait, I'm not just marryinganybody, I'm marrying her."
- Yeah.- Before we got married,
I knew who he was,I knew his dreams,
I knew the things he wantedto achieve in life.
So I have to understand that...
what I want to ask and happenisn't easy for him.
- So, I will allow...- Everything.
- True.- He has to love you
even if you dyeyour hair red today.
True. He even tells me,
"You know, if I countedyour hair colors,
I'd have had that manyex-girlfriends."
Whatever your hair color is,I just mirror it.
- Yeah.- Yeah, like that.
Me, too.That's why he loves me.
He says, "When I'm with you,I have a wife."
Then at night,"Oh, my grandpa is here."
[LAUGHING]
Oh come on,that's too much.
Calling you "Grandfather"is too much.
You know, it's not like that,because there are times
when I'm not around,he plays with my wig.
- Mm. Does he wear it?- He takes videos of those.
No, I told him, "You playwith my wigs for your TikToks."
Then he said,"It's my way to feel close
even when you're not here."
- Aww.- Aww.
So he can still feelthat connection with you
- when he wakes up.- Yes, right, through the wig.
Where do you see yourselfin 50 years?
Still in the Philippines, maybe?In Mindanao? In the province?
- Perhaps Forbes Park or Japan?- I feel like...
Where would you like to seeeach other in 50 years?
Our dream is to have a farm...
...with a small house.Very simple.
I mean, we're very grateful
for all the things that wewere able to experience
because of Palagi.
We went on tour.Imagine, Vice...
After our In Between tourand Sarili Nating Mundo tour,
we'd have done a totalof 65 shows.
Seventy if we include the firstleg orSarili Nating Mundotour.
So...
Right now, we're looking forwardfor things to slow down a bit.
[VICE]You want to enjoy some peace.
- Correct.- And you envision a farm life.
- Yes.- I'd like that too.
I can already hear the goatscalling me like, "Memeeh!"
- [LAUGHTER]- [TJ] Nice one!
[KZ] That's so funny!
- [TJ] Witty!- Right?
"Memeeh!"
Must be nice.
Then you'll wake up withfresh air brushing your face,
catching a whiff of...carabao droppings.
And you'll be like,"Oh! The smell of nature!"
I suggest you nameyour kambingan (goat shed)
"KZ Kambingan."
[VICE] Oh, I love that!"KZ Kambingan!"
Wow, wow.
- [VICE CHUCKLES]- I'd be so proud
to have my namein Meme's farm.
[VICE] Yeah, I love the idea.
How do you handle changes?
Because changeis inevitable, right?
What would you doif TJ changes?
What if one day, he comes homeand you notice he has changed?
Like, you realize he's slowly...
- ...growing a pair of boobs.- [LAUGHS]
- That's...- Instead of going on tour...
...he actually got it donein Thailand.
He still loves youbut he's a new person now.
- [TETAY] He also dyed his hair.- Yes. What if?
What if he comes homewith Barbie arms?
He'd have smaller armsthan I have.
Well, that's...
How do you deal with change?
That's part of your commitment.
To love every versionof your spouse.
Because you too will change,
and you'd want them to give youthe same grace.
If I want him to love mein all of my ups and downs,
I must love allthe versions of TJ.
We've been togetherfor 11 years,
so we've seen each other'sups and downs.
[VICE] What's your favoriteversion of TJ?
When he's up or down?
[LAUGHS]
[SILLY SOUND EFFECTS]
Sounds suggestive.
Because people say you'll seesomeone's real nature
either when they're at the topor at the bottom.
Because that affectssomeone's attitude.
When they're at the top,
you may find out how badof a person they are.
- When they're at the bottom--- [TJ] But KZ is...
Her attitude never changes,
so I'd rather see herstay on top.
- You want her on top?- I want her on top.
Because she neverchanges her attitude.
When she's on top,where are you?
I'm... [LAUGHS]
- Beside me.- Huh?
I'm here. [CHUCKLES]I'm just here.
But does she also go downsometimes?
- Yes.- [AUDIENCE SQUEAL]
[VICE] That's necessaryin relationships, right?
In a relationship, you can'thave just one staying on top.
You must both go down sometime.You need to meet halfway.
Yes, that's true.
And you must be therefor all... levels.
- What are we talking about?- I'd like to ask too.
I'm also lost.What are we talking about again?
What are you asking us?
What show are we on?
- But seriously--- Speaking of change...
I read somewhere--Or did I watch it?
A child asked his father,
"Why hasn't your lovefor Mommy changed?"
The father replied,"Who said it hasn't changed?
It has changed." The kidwas confused. He then asked,
"How come? You've been togetherfor more than 50 years."
The father explained,"Your mother has changed.
She's not the same lady whoI fell in love with years ago.
She has changed in many ways.
And my love for her has evolvedalong with all those changes.
I love all versions of her."
- [TJ] Exactly.- [KZ] That's how it should be.
When the wifegained stretch marks,
the father also changed.
Before, he liked girls who arepetite and have smooth skin.
Now, he wants a womanwho's a little chubby,
and thinks stretch marksare beautiful
because of his wife.
Before, he liked womenwho always dress up nicely.
But his wife stoppedcaring about style.
Now, he'd rather see his wifeprioritize comfort
while they're taking careof their baby.
Every time she changes,he changes too.
[KZ] That's how it should be.
Earlier, we were talkingabout different versions of us
and how we handleups and downs.
When I was at the bottom...
When I didn't even havelove for myself...
He-- You're laughing.
- I know that look!- Don't judge me.
[KZ] She was about to makeanother joke!
- I saw it too!- She was like...
- [LAUGHTER]- No! I... I thought...
I found the topic interestingso I did this.
[KZ] She was like,"She said that word."
- "She said the word."- "She said bottom. Bottom!"
I saw her!
- But, no--- So, bottom.
[LAUGHTER]
[VICE] You mean your lowestpoint in your life, right?
Yes, when I was at my lowest,
I actually triedto break up with him.
I said, "I'm breaking upwith you right now
because I'm unable to give youthe love that you deserve."
I couldn't give him attention.Because at that time...
Oh, gosh. Wow.
That was one of thedarkest times of my life.
I was depressed.Like, really depressed.
And, um...
I was pushing people away,including TJ.
I told him,"I'm breaking up with you
because I can't bear todrag you with me
in this dark pitof my depression."
Because I sawhow it affected him, so...
I told him we should break up.
And he said, "If you can'tafford to love right now,
I'll love for the both of us."
And he'd ask me every time,"Let's pray, love."
But during that time,I would refuse to pray.
I would refuse toacknowledge God.
And he'd say...
"If you can't pray right now,I'll pray for the both of us."
That's why I'm so grateful now.Lord, thank You so much.
It's like You made sureI had someone to lean on
during the darkest timeof my life.
[VICE] Wow.
You're blessed to have foundsomeone like him.
Yes, I'm very blessed.That's why I'm so grateful.
- I always tease him, but...- [VICE COOING]
- ...I'm grateful for him.- [VICE] Aww!
[APPLAUSE]
[VICE] Beautiful.That's beautiful.
They've shared so manyunexpected stories, right?
Now, they're going toshare more...
and we're going to guessif they really happened or not.
Okay?
They have more stories to share,
but it's time to putour thinking caps on.
Vince, Tetay, Verna,come here.
Let's move on to our game ofTrot (truth) or Charot (lie).
And we call this portionDeep Truth.
In Deep Truth, you willeach give a statement,
and we're going to guessif it's Trot or Charot.
[TETAY] Yes.
Everything you shared earlierwere all true, right?
Now, you have tomake us guess.
If we guess wrong,we have to do a consequence.
Okay, so who'll go first?
TJ, go.
TJ Monterde,what is your Deep Statement?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Take it out.- Should I read it?
[VICE] Yes, please.
[VICE] TJ's taking it out!
[VINCE CHUCKLING]
- [TETAY] He's pulling it out.- What's TJ's Deep Statement?
My Deep Statement is,
"I wore KZ's pantiesto a concert."
- [LAUGHTER]- [VICE] I don't believe it.
Why would you wearher panties?
I left my extra briefs.
- [VICE] You left your briefs?- My extra briefs.
Wait a minute. You left...
- You left your briefs--- [TJ] I was wearing one before.
[VICE] So you left your briefs.
You had to change,but you didn't have extras.
- Yes.- So you wore KZ's panties.
She had extra.
Oh! I thought you tookwhat she was wearing!
I thought she loved youso much,
she was like, "Love, I got you.
- I'll let you wear my panties."- She sacrificed hers?
No, she let me borrowher extra panties
because we were about toperform a full-length concert.
Good thing it fit.
Oh, right.She's well-endowed too.
- [LAUGHTER]- [SILLY SOUND EFFECTS]
- It was stretchable.- He stretched it out!
Her panties are stretchable.So I wore her panties.
[VERNA] They are stretchable?How many did you put on?
It was stretchable...
Would you ever agreeto wear a panty?
- Maybe.- Have you worn one before?
- Yes.- How did it feel?
Well, it was... in between.[CHUCKLES]
[TETAY] Refreshing, right?
What do you meanby "in between"?
In between... I mean...
There are two balls, right?It got in between them.
- [LAUGHTER]- Oh! It parted!
It's like when Mosesparted the Red Sea!
That can hurt, especially ifit was made of lace!
- That can cut you!- True.
It can actually hurt your...
Yeah, that's painful.
You didn't knowhow to tuck it in?
Maybe he wore it backwards.Perhaps it was a thong.
[VICE] It's called "T-back"for a reason!
[TETAY] The stringshould be at the back.
- I just remember it was thin.- Wearing it backwards must've--
[VICE]Whose panties did you wear?
[VERNA]Where did you get them?
What happened was,
my friends and I were drunk.
- [VICE] And then?- We found a pair of panties.
You know how guys arewhen we get drunk.
I lost a bet, so...
So men really do that.
Because I remember Ogie Alcasidtelling us a similar story.
He asked us, "Did you alsogo through that phase
where you would wear panties?"
[TJ] A phase?That's different.
So he had a group of friendswho were all male.
They'd find panties andwould wear them all for fun.
Vhong was like,"We didn't do that."
And I was like, "You did that?You're all cracked in the head."
Ogie said, "It was normal!My friends and I all did it!"
Now, I'm not surprisedyou did it too.
Well, Ogie and I went tothe same university. [CHUCKLES]
Yeah, you'll get along.
- You wore panties to a concert?- Yes, the whole show.
- Sarili Nating Mundo in Vegas.- How did it feel?
- It felt cool.- [LAUGHTER]
- I didn't know it was comfy.- What was it made of? Lace?
[VERNA] Was it lace?
What was it made of?
What brand?
I remember it was all black.
[TETAY] What do you think?
"I wore KZ's pantiesto a concert."
What do you think?
Trot or Charot?
- Trot!- Trot!
[VICE]I think I'll believe them.
It looks like they knowevery single detail
about TJ and KZ's life,so I'll choose Trot.
- How about you?- I think Trot.
Me, too.
[OVERLAPPING SHOUTSFROM AUDIENCE]
[VICE] Do you wear panties?
- Yes.- [VICE] May I see them?
Just the strap.
No, I'm wearing high-waistboxers right now.
[LAUGHTER]
But on normal days,I wear panties, like you.
- [VICE] I think it's Trot.- [VERNA] Me, too.
Tetay thinks it's Charot.
- Because...- [AUDIENCE SHOUTING]
[VICE] Why do you think so?
I think most guys don't mindnot wearing underwear.
It's okay for themto go commando...
- ...or wear it inside out.- Than wear panties?
You've got a point.They might rather go commando.
Because some guysreally don't wear underwear.
[VINCE] Some call it"emotional support."
Do you feel emotionsdown there?!
- Emotional support?- I think it's Charot.
But since they say it's Trot,I'll believe them.
- [VERNA] I think it's Trot.- Okay, Trot! So...
TJ, it's time to revealyour Deep Truth!
Did you really wear KZ's pantiesto a concert?
Is it Trot or Charot?
[TETAY] Okay!
"I wore KZ's pantiesto a concert."
This statement is...
[VERNA, AUDIENCE] Trot!
Trot!
- Yes!- [LAUGHTER]
Tetay guessed wrong!
- You knew, KZ?- Yeah.
Tell them the whole backstory.
- I'll give you all the details.- It's Trot.
We were on tour.
It was the Las Vegas legof Sarili Nating Mundo.
The last of a three-night show.
- Three consecutive shows.- Yes, three consecutive shows.
Houston, New York,then Las Vegas.
They're all far apart, right?You know how it goes on tour.
By the time you arriveat the airport,
chances are you're so tiredor overstimulated.
My bags exceededthe weight limit.
So, I asked our drummer if Icould put my stuff in his bag.
A whole packing cube.
What's inside it?
- All my underwear.- All of them?
I put them all in his luggage.
So, when we arrived in Vegas,
KZ and I went straight to restat the hotel.
By the time we werescheduled to change,
our drummer was alreadyat the venue for soundcheck.
I was like, "Oh my god. I don'thave any clean underwear."
You're not usedto going commando?
No, I don't do commando.
And I hadn't had the chance tochange since the night before.
So it was dirty.
I didn't want to wear it again.
- Plus, it was hot in Vegas.- Yes, exactly.
We didn't have time,so she said...
"I have extra panties.You want?" [CHUCKLES]
[VICE] What if...
...she only had a spare bra?At least it has two cups, right?
- I don't know.- Just fold the cups together...
...and tie it with the straplike a G-string!
So, I wore her panties.
That's when I learnedpanties are so comfy.
[VICE] True.
Since I started wearing panties,I've never worn briefs again.
- [TJ] Same here.- It's pretty comfortable.
- [LAUGHTER]- [VERNA] You too?!
- Just kidding! Sorry!- That was fast!
So good!
No wonder your pantieskeep disappearing.
No wonder I only havea few panties left, huh?
I told you, didn't I? You haveto embrace the changes.
Exactly! We might end upsharing a wardrobe.
[VICE] You know what's funny?
Ever since we started, untilnow that we're almost done,
your feet haven't touchedthe floor once.
- Yeah, it's comfortable.- Because sitting like this,
it feels like a job interview.
[VICE GIGGLES]
Back on The Buzz, when they'dhave those episodes
where someone wouldexpose a family?
- "I'll finally confess..."- [LAUGHTER]
- The Buzz?- [LAUGHTER]
I can't do that becausemy chair's too high.
And those "Breaking my silence"moments?
Yes.
- It kinda looks like that.- Like an expose.
But when you're sittinglike this, look at us.
We look ridiculous.
It looks so bad.
When you eatat a fast-food place,
do you sit in a high chair?
Oh, no. I don't fit.
I bet you always sitin front, right?
The seat with the high footrest.
Exactly. That's true.
Where it's warm,near the engine.
- [BOTH LAUGH]- True.
Now, you give us the Deep Truth.
What's KZ's deep statement?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- KZ's deep statement is...- [TETAY] Let's check it out.
[VINCE] KZ's deep statement.
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
[VERNA] Oh, my gosh!
Read it, KZ.
"Caught buying an adult toy."
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What kind of adult toy?
- Just an adult toy.- [TJ LAUGHING]
For her or for him?
- For both of them.- Yeah.
- [VINCE] Where?- Oh.
- In another country?- Yes.
Yeah, because it'sembarrassing to buy one here.
Even buying condoms herecan feel embarrassing.
People judge you.
So when we're abroad,that's where we buy them, right?
You bought a wholesuitcase full, right?
You even bought theglow-in-the-dark one, right?
Let's focus on KZ right now.
You were caught buying...
What country was that?America?
Europe.
- Oh.- Amsterdam.
So there were two of you?
There were two of us.We both got caught.
So after you went to the outlet,you went straight there?
[CHUCKLING]
- "Oh, there's a sale here!"- Yeah, it was on sale too.
Hmm.
What about you?
Is that an adult toy?
Is this an adult toy?
- What?- I feel like it's not real.
Why?
I feel like they don't evenneed one.
How did KZ go frombeing a virgin to being so...
- So wild.- Oh, why?
They're a sex-positive couple.
They're sex-positive.
It's part of, you know...
Like, part of the adventureis exploring.
There's nothing wrongwith using toys.
Yeah. I use them too.
- Even my mom uses toys.- [VICE] Yes.
She even messed aroundwith the doorknob.
I saw yours in the drawer.
Alright, I'll go with Trot.
- What about you?- I feel like it's Charot.
- Because...- It suits you to say Charot.
- Say it again.- I feel like it's Charot.
- [VICE CHUCKLING]- It sounds so classy!
Because, you know, Europehas a pretty liberated culture.
So why would youget caught there?
- It's legal there.- So who caught you, anyway?
Right?
Who caught us? Uh...
Who was it again?
[TETAY] Oh!
We got caught selling them.
- [LAUGHTER]- You're messing with us.
[VERNA] It's not accurate!
[VICE CHUCKLING]
You're fooling us.
Yes.
[VICE] Last question...
Did you just recently buy the toy,
or have you had it for a while?
- When was that trip?- Back in 2023.
Whose idea was it to gointo the adult store?
- TJ's.- Did you use it?
- No.- [VERNA] Oh, it's possible!
You didn't use it?
[TETAY] What a waste.Give it to me.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, you just tried it on?
No, not that either.
That's Charot.
- It's Charot for me, too.- It's Charot for me, too.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
It doesn't seem like KZ,you know, even TJ...
Maybe five years from now,if ever...
It's Charot.So, KZ, it's time.
Time for you to revealthe Deep Truth to us.
Is it true that you got caughtbuying an adult toy?
Trot or Charot?
[TETAY] What?!
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
Charot!
Charot with a little bitof Trot mixed in.
- [KZ GIGGLES]- Huh?
Charot with a little bitof Trot?
Charot with a little bitof Trot.
- Why?- Because...
Here you go. Excuse me, babe.
[LAUGHTER]
You always forget!
- You're blocking two cameras!- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
There you go.
It's charot with a littlebit of truth, Vice.
We really did go to Amsterdam.
And when we got there,it was freezing.
Then we went to theRed Light District.
So we were walkingand walking...
But we underestimatedhow cold it would be.
So we'd go into any storethat was open.
- They had heaters inside.- Exactly.
When we went inside,
of course, there wereall kinds of stores
in the Red Light District.
So when we went in,we warmed ourselves up there.
We were basically justusing their heater.
Then the saleslady probablynoticed us and thought...
"These two have been herefor like 15 minutes."
Then someone came up to us."Excuse me?
Do you need anything?Do you need help with anything?
Do you need me to explainanything to you?"
Then TJ and I panicked.
And then TJ went,"How do you use this?"
[LAUGHTER]
- We didn't--- [VICE] What was he holding?
- We don't know!- But it's like this.
- It's like this.- [VICE] Oh, that's a dildo!
[KZ] Oh, no, it wasn't a dildo.Oh, sorry.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
We both didn't knowwhat it was.
But then it suddenly wentlike that.
He looked at me,and then I said,
"Y-Yeah, how do you use?"
And, in their culture,that shyness doesn't exist.
- It only exists in ours.- [VICE] Yeah.
They really explained it.
This is you, this is her,and then you--
They were really acting it out!
And TJ kept looking at mewith a face that was asking,
"Do we just buy it?"
- [VICE] Did you buy it?- No, but he said,
"We'll just look around first.We'll think about it."
So we roamed around, and thenwe heard some Filipinos.
They're like, "Oh my!"So we quickly ran away.
[VICE] Oh, a Filipino saw you!
But, yeah,we weren't there to buy.
We just wanted to usetheir heater.
[VICE] That's crazy.I'll share a similar experience.
I have a friend.
[VICE LAUGHING]
[KZ] Is it you? Just kidding.
No, she's a celebrity friend.
We went on a vacation.
She's a celebrity.You know her very well.
Wait, never mind.I won't tell the story.
[KZ] But you already started it!
You already started it!
We won't leaveunless you share it.
No, it's just funny.We were with her mom.
We went to America with her mom,
- And then--- [TJ] Is it a man or a woman?
- A woman.- [TJ] A woman, okay.
Who was with her mom!Just kidding, go on.
She was with her mom'cause she's still young!
Her mom was there 'cause--But she's not a minor!
- She's not a minor.- [KZ] Okay, okay, okay.
She was in her late twenties.
I asked her to come with me toan adult shop to buy a condom.
She kept looking aroundthe store,
and she seemed really curious!So...
I bought her a toy.
I said, "You're probably too shyto buy, so I'll buy it for you.
And then she said, "Oh, Vice!"But I still bought her one.
When we were on our wayback to the Philippines,
She asked if she could putthe toy in my stuff first
'cause she's with her mom,so I let her.
Unfortunately,my baggage exceeded.
I put it in her trolleywithout her knowing
'cause that was hers.
We were on our way to the x-ray,
and her momwas carrying her trolley.
When it got into the x-ray,they were flagged!
Her trolley went another way!
The staff asked,"Is this your luggage?"
- "Yeah." Yes.- [TJ] Her mom?
They askedif she prepared it herself,
her mom said yes.
"Can you open it, please?"
When she opened it,they saw the toy.
- [TJ] Oh my god!- [VICE] They took it out!
Her mom was like,"This is not mine!"
She even asked who bought it."Oh, that's Vice's!"
I said, "That's not mine!Why would I buy that?"
There were even Filipinos!
We were so embarrassed'cause they kept looking at us.
Let's just call herby the name--
- [TJ LAUGHING]- [VICE SCREAMING]
But that's it.Her mom scolded us.
[TETAY] You won't give a clue?
- Huh?- [TETAY] Give us a clue.
I won't.But she's now in her thir--
She's over 70 years old now.
So you won't know who she is.
Right? When there's a Filipino,you know you'll get judged.
Other nationalitieswouldn't care.
Even if you show it,
even if you wearit while you're walking,
- it's okay.- [KZ] That's right.
But I don't thinkwe'll reach that far.
So, charot--
Is it charot?
- Charot with some truth.- Charot with some truth.
But with TJ earlier,you were wrong.
You said charotabout him wearing a panty,
so you have to dothe punishment.
What's the punishment, Vince?Read it.
You have to squat dipon the floor like a frog
and you have to go aroundthe stage.
[VICE] Can you do it?Aren't you in pain tonight?
I don't think so.But we'll find out, sister.
[VICE]Sister, don't you have gout?
- You might fight me.- So, like a frog?
- You'll act like a frog. Yes.- And I have to squat?
- In her long gout competition.- Yes, Gout-emala (Guatamela)!
So, there, squat.
And then? Is that correct?Show the right posture, Vince.
- Since you go to the gym.- Go lower.
- Go lower.- Lower?
[VICE] Lower. And then?
- Go. Show me.- [VINCE CHUCKLES]
- Show me, show me.- [VICE] You won that round.
- Yeah!- Show me.
Okay, I can do it.Okay, go.
- See? See?- [VINCE CHUCKLES]
- Is this what you want?- [VICE] Go to sir.
Okay, we can walk now.Just kidding.
Thank you very much, KZ and TJ!
- Let's clap for them.- Thank you!
It's so fun!
I really liked our conversation
- 'cause it was fun!- Thank you.
There were so many revelations,
and, at the same time,it was heartwarming.
We talked about nice thingsthat it made me happy.
I feel proudof our conversation.
It seemed to have substance.
- That's right.- That's true.
Thank you, TJ and KZ,for being so generous,
and for being so trusting.
- Thank you, Vice. Yeah.- We revealed a lot.
Yeah, well...
GGVis the perfect avenue for us
and for them to reallyget to know us at that level.
- Are you happy?- Yes. Thank you, Vice.
I missed this show so much.
Thank you. Thank you so much.Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, and congratulations,TJ and KZ.
Your success...
is just staggering.
You and your songs.
We're all excitedto hear some new songs.
I know you alwaysput your hearts into your craft.
You always put outso heartfelt songs for us.
I'm looking forwardto seeing you
experience the bestof everything.
- Thank you.- Thank you, Vice.
- In life.- Thank you.
- Do you have any shows?- Oh, yeah.
We're currently doingour In Between tour,
just like we mentioned earlier.
Uh... This is our...
It's like the end of our tourfor the past two years.
We've done 20 shows this year,
and now, we're downto our last two shows.
Our last two showswill be in the Middle East,
for ourKapamilyasandKapusos.
October 9 at the QatarNational Convention Center
and the grand finaleof In Between
will be at theCoca-Cola Arena in Dubai, UAE.
Oh, that venue is huge!
Yes, for ticketsand more details
about the final two shows,
please make sure to visitdrelegantevents.com.
We'll see you there,Kapamilyas and Kapusos!
- Thank you.- Love you, KZ and TJ!
- Thank you very much, Vice!- Thank you!
You can watch GGVunfiltered version on iWant.
We feel the laughter worldwide.
So, subscribe to iWant.
And we'll see you again,Kapamilyas and Kapusos
only here on the best viceevery Sunday night.
This is...
[IN UNISON] Gandang Gabi Vice!
[CHEERFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]